<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Ethan Escareño Rosano</title>
    <link>https://ethaan.js.org/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Ethan Escareño Rosano</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 22:11:01 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ethaan.js.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>You Might Not Need Apollo (client)</title>
      <link>https://ethaan.js.org/posts/2020/07/you-might-not-need-apollo-client/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 22:11:01 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ethaan.js.org/posts/2020/07/you-might-not-need-apollo-client/</guid>
      <description>NOTE Here we are just talking about Apollo client implementation, not Apollo Server, that could be another topic.
So you will start a new project, and you are luckly enought to choose the stack for this new project, for the frontend you decide to go with React, for state managment you think is OK to keep it simple and use hooks, while for sharing state React.Context can do the work, also TailwindCSS seems the option to go, and you will use Parcel, Rollup or Webpack, and now you have to decide about how to get domain data, so you decide to use Apollo Client, since you have an Apollo backend, you might want to take a look into using something like SWR + Prisma/request.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cover Letter</title>
      <link>https://ethaan.js.org/posts/2020/04/cover-letter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 19:19:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ethaan.js.org/posts/2020/04/cover-letter/</guid>
      <description>Recluiter. Hi.
As my Whats up  describe me at a personal level, this post inteent to describe myself as a Software Engineer.
Backgroud. Been OK with the idea of spent 18hrs a day in front of the computer since i was 13years old, but not doing actually something productive until i was 20years old~.
Work for a big IT company on the IT departament for 4years before switching to a remote-programming job, since then been wearing many hats on many startups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tuples for Fun</title>
      <link>https://ethaan.js.org/posts/2020/04/tuples-for-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 18:18:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ethaan.js.org/posts/2020/04/tuples-for-fun/</guid>
      <description>As I have already mentioned on my previous posts, Python Javascript(ts) and Swift are some of my favorite languages out there, I really enjoy writting software with them, and this past days I got into how tuples work in these 3 languages.
Tuples So what is a tuple? there might be many different ways to describe a Tuple Data type, but the easiest one I can think of right now is like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby Steps Typescript</title>
      <link>https://ethaan.js.org/posts/2020/03/baby-steps-typescript/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 13:16:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ethaan.js.org/posts/2020/03/baby-steps-typescript/</guid>
      <description>Intro Typescript as the repo and many other people mention is a superset of JavaScript that compiles to clean JavaScript output.
NOTE If you are Totally new on Typescript, check out this amazing Understanding TypeScript’s type notation blog post
If you are unsure if Typescript is or not a superset and what actually superset and subset means I recommend you to read this SO post
Saying this, let&amp;rsquo;s start writting some JS and then the equivalent in Typescript.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whats Up</title>
      <link>https://ethaan.js.org/posts/2020/03/whats-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 14:06:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ethaan.js.org/posts/2020/03/whats-up/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve always thought on writting stuff on the WWW, but I never got full hands to it, until now, so I would like to welcome you to what intends to be my new blog/site where you can find all about the things that I&amp;rsquo;m most interested in, you can expect to find stuff such as:
 Music (mostly punk) Programming (Python, Javascript, Swift and bit of everything) WWII Podcast RPG games  Before digging into different topics I would like introduce myself.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>