<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Ethan Escareño Rosano</title>
    <link>https://ethaan.js.org/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Ethan Escareño Rosano</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 18:18:03 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ethaan.js.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tuples for Fun</title>
      <link>https://ethaan.js.org/posts/2020/04/tuples-for-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 18:18:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ethaan.js.org/posts/2020/04/tuples-for-fun/</guid>
      <description>As i already mention on my previous posts, Python Javascript(ts) and Swift are some of my favorite languages out there, i really enjoy writting programs with them, and this past days i come into how tuples works on this 3 languages, which one have a better API that the other (spoiler: Python)
Tuples So whats a tuple? there might be many different ways to describe a Tuple Data type, but the easiest one i can think of right now is like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby Steps Typescript</title>
      <link>https://ethaan.js.org/posts/2020/03/baby-steps-typescript/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 13:16:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ethaan.js.org/posts/2020/03/baby-steps-typescript/</guid>
      <description>Intro Typescript as the repo and many other people mention is a superset of JavaScript that compiles to clean JavaScript output.
NOTE If you are Totally new on Typescript, check out this amazing Understanding TypeScript’s type notation blog post
If you are unsure if Typescript is or not a superset and what actually superset and subset means i recommend you to read this SO post
Saying this, lets start writting some JS and then the equivalent on Typescript.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whats Up</title>
      <link>https://ethaan.js.org/posts/2020/03/whats-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 14:06:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ethaan.js.org/posts/2020/03/whats-up/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;been always thinking on writting stuff on the WWW, but never really get full into it, until now, so i would like to give the welcome to what inteend to be be my new blog/site where you can find all about the things that i&amp;rsquo;m most inerested on, you can expect to find stuff such as
 Music (mostly punk) Programming (Python, Javascritp, Swift and bit of everything) WWII Podcast RPG games  Before digging into different topics i would like Introduce myself, my name is Ethan Escareño Rosano, and i&amp;rsquo;m from Reynosa, Tamaulipas, Mexico at the moment of writting this post i work as a Software Engineer on different projects around the globe, more exactly on Web Development, but i hope to someday in the short-future start my own startup</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>