<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ethan Escareño Rosano</title>
    <link>https://ethaan.js.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ethan Escareño Rosano</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2020 15:46:42 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ethaan.js.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What a year</title>
      <link>https://ethaan.js.org/posts/2020/12/what-a-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2020 15:46:42 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ethaan.js.org/posts/2020/12/what-a-year/</guid>
      <description>2020 was a weird year, it was the year where some us are stuck in our homes since March, and we still here, going strong.
There is much i can say about 2020, but i don&amp;rsquo;t really want to romanticize this year, it was a shitty year and thats it(period)
But as i always tell my wife/friends, i try to grab the best of every scenario, and thats what i did, how?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cover Letter</title>
      <link>https://ethaan.js.org/posts/2020/04/cover-letter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 19:19:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ethaan.js.org/posts/2020/04/cover-letter/</guid>
      <description>Recluiter. Hi.
As my Whats up  describe me at a personal level, this post inteent to describe myself as a Software Engineer.
Backgroud. Been OK with the idea of spent 18hrs a day in front of the computer since i was 13years old, but not doing actually something productive until i was 20years old~.
Work for a big IT company on the IT departament for 4years before switching to a remote-programming job, since then been wearing many hats on many startups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whats Up</title>
      <link>https://ethaan.js.org/posts/2020/03/whats-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 14:06:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ethaan.js.org/posts/2020/03/whats-up/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve always thought on writting stuff on the WWW, but I never got full hands to it, until now, so I would like to welcome you to what intends to be my new blog/site where you can find all about the things that I&amp;rsquo;m most interested in, you can expect to find stuff such as:
 Music (mostly punk) Programming (Python, Javascript, Swift and bit of everything) WWII Podcast RPG games  Before digging into different topics I would like introduce myself.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>